Good morning.
I'm home.
9:05 in the morning
It's 9:05 in the morning.
I woke up at 9:05 a.m.
I'm going to be in Nagoya for a lilly
I'm going to do my makeup.
Here's the primer.
Today is Nagoya.
I'm in Nagoya, so...
What's in Nagoya?
Tebasaki?
I heard someone say they have chicken wings.
I've never had it.
I've never eaten in Japan.
Surprisingly, there are a lot of them.
Yoshinoya and Matsuya.
I'd never eaten at Yoshinoya and Matsuya.
What's this?
What is this?
What is this? Ha-ha-ha... This is Clio, but it's only about this big, so I'll just paint the top.
I'm not going to paint the bottom.
And...
I apply the darkest part of the brown eyeshadow.
The darkest part.
the darkest part.
Like this.
With a hot water brush
Just like that.
It's thick, isn't it?
That's all right.
Then use a brush like this.
See?
Yeah, blur it.
Just at the corners of the eyes.
Right here, because I have round eyes.
I want to make them look a little bit rounder.
You see? Just a little bit.
I feel like...
It's just a little bit.
It's a little longer.
Okay, so it's the same again.
This one.
The darkest color.
We're going to put the darkest color around here.
The crease.
Put it on the crease.
Not just the triangle.
Here.
Put it right here.
My eyes are a little far apart.
I don't know.
I don't want to draw a world line.
A little bit here.
I want to put a little bit of black here, not as much as I want to draw the world line, but a little bit of black here.
I want to make it black.
I want to make it look closer.
It's just a matter of feeling.
I don't care if it's different or not.
I'm applying eyeshadow here.
I'm applying it here.
That's all.
Surrounding the eyes makes a big difference.
If you surround your eyes with eye shadow, it makes a big difference in the power of your eyes.
Those who have it surrounded, those who don't.
Do you see?
This is very important.
So, I'm going to draw eyeliner.
Love Liner
Black.
Wow!
I just wanted to talk about the members.
We were rehearsing for a one-man show.
Not a one-man rehearsal.
At some rehearsal...
I was...
I took some medicine and got sleepy.
Before that rehearsal
I was feeling depressed.
But today, we were going to play "Seitenari".
I was doing it.
And the members around me seemed to be having so much fun.
I don't know why, even though I'm feeling pretty down
But seeing the members makes me happy.
They're talking about how they're having a good time.
It makes me happy too.
I think this environment is wonderful.
It's wonderful to be influenced by the members and be happy.
I thought
I thought, "You must like the members.
I'm thinking about it every day.
I mean, I think about it every day.
At the Wambar
I think there was a song project and a dance project
During the rehearsal
I saw everyone's dance
I think it's because we're
We were performing together.
objectively
It's rare to see it objectively.
I've seen it.
You saw it for the first time.
The teacher was there.
I was like, "Turn around and really try it.
It was like...
Look at that.
I was just...
I was overwhelmed.
The way all six of them expressed themselves
The way they showed it was totally different.
But
They're all the same.
But they're all here in winter.
But when I look at here
It's totally different.
I think that's what's interesting.
And the skills of each one of them
The skills of each one of us have improved a lot.
I don't know what to call it, but I cried.
I cried.
I was so happy to be able to work with such a wonderful group of people.
To be honest.
I'm crazy about you.
I'm having so much fun every day that I'm thinking about you. It's an orange blush.
A makeup artist was using it, and I thought it was a cute color, so I got it as a Christmas present.
Lip recommendation
Yves Saint Laurent.
I got it for Christmas last year, and I haven't worn it since then.
I got this for Christmas last year, and I don't have any color at all!
My makeup is almost done!
I just arrived at my room.
Good morning, Ms. Kins.
Good morning.
I said hello to everyone at Ebidan Nagoya.
They were so cute.
Hey, wait.
The bottom one.
Isn't that bad?
The youngest is in the third grade.
The oldest is in eighth grade.
That's not good.
Really?
It's so tight.
Oh, no.
I thought, "Oh no,
I don't need it.
I felt like we're too old for each other.
Yeah, we're too far apart.
Isn't eighth grade too much? Good morning. Good morning. I can't believe how far apart we are... 10 years!
Good morning.
You are here in Wa-Nagoya today.
Good morning
We'll be back soon and rehearsals will begin.
It's our first time on stage.
Certainly the first time on stage.
It was your first time on stage, wasn't it? Indeed. It was the first time for us, but that's why we want to do our best.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
Mr. Yabana is going to make a big fan when we come together for work.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
Okay, then. I'm totally fine. Well, then, please. I'm sure that if the inside of a lost bone springs up tonight...
Not only true.
Thank you for today... oh, wait a minute, sorry, what is it?
Thank you for today, and we'll keep working together.
I look forward to working with you.
He says it's a cool pose.
Cool pose.
Hey. Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, that looks good, thank you. Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Thank you...
You're early. Thank you for the bath.
To get this to you all.
Please buy this one at the one-man show, it's a limited edition.
You can only get it there.
It's a patterned one, so...
Please put it up in your home.
It's autographed and signed by all of you.
Is today's bento good?
It's too small!
He's eating so well!
And what are you doing today? Oh, wow... The remaining three male members are staying at Amu's house.
How was your first time in Nagoya today?
Sumabushi was delicious.
No, no, no. Everyone was so nice and it was a lot of fun.
How is it?
It was cold outside, but everyone was warm. It was cold outside, but everyone was warm.
I can fly wings!
I can fly!
Well, then, I'd like to present you all with the bones of a chicken wing.
Se-no!
Poof!
Bye bye!